http://www.hibiscus.org/privacy.php

Search this site:
Privacy Statement for Hibiscus.ORG
Hibiscus.ORG
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site:
Hibiscus.ORG
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information. This information is used solely to provide aggregate data such as browser statistics, country of origin and frequency of page views.
No information relating to individuals is obtained or extracted, directly or indirectly.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies.
While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are
collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally
identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal
information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites.
Hibiscus.ORG
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
info@hibiscus.org
Introduction  |
Articles  |
Species  |
Culinary information
FAQs  |
Links  |
Contact Us  |
Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2000-2011 hibiscus.org All rights reserved.
See also our other site The Web Hymns Network - http://www.webhymns.net Featuring a selection of classic hymns performed on piano and organ, with lyrics, free for reuse
